Yun-Yun Tsai

alice103000004@gmail.com (+886)973-798-908

RESEARCH INTERESTS

I'm currently a research assistant in National Tsing Hua University, under the supervision of Dr. Tsung-Yi Ho and cosupervision of Dr. Pin-Yu Chen from IBM AI Watson research. My research focuses on Artificial Intelligence Security, adversarial machine learning toward the robustness of deep neural networks, including attack, defense and robust evaluation.

EDUCATION

National Tsing Hua University

Hsinchu, Taiwan

M.S. in Computer Science Department

Sep. 2018 – Jun. 2020

Advisor: Dr. Tsung-Yi Ho

Overall GPA: 4.18 / 4.3

- Visiting Student at the HSL at University of Florida (UF), Gainesville, Florida

Mar. 2019 - Aug. 2019

Advisor: Dr. Yier Jin

National Tsing Hua University

Hsinchu, Taiwan

B.S. in Computer Science Department

Sep. 2014 – Jun. 2018

Overall GPA: 3.5 / 4.3, Last 60 GPA: 3.89 / 4.3

PUBLICATIONS

- Yun-Yun Tsai, Pin-Yu Chen, Tsung-Yi Ho, "Transfer Learning without Knowing, Reprogramming black box machine learning model with scarce data and limited resources." in Proceeding of International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2020.
- Yun-Yun Tsai, Pin-Yu Chen, Tsung-Yi Ho, "Adversarial Machine Learning for Social Good: Reprogramming black box machine learning model with scarce data and limited resources." Advances in Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS) NewInML Workshop, Poster, 2019.
- Honggang Yu, Kaichen Yang, Teng Zhang, Yun-Yun Tsai, Tsung-Yi Ho, Yier Jin, "CloudLeak: Large-Scale Deep Learning Models Stealing Through Adversarial Examples." in Proceeding of Network and Distributed System Security Symposium (NDSS), 2020.
- Ta-Wei Huang, Yun-Yun Tsai, Chung-Wei Lin, Tsung-Yi Ho, "Vehicle Sequence Reordering with Cooperative Adaptive Cruise Control." In Proceeding of Design, Automation & Test in Europe Conference & Exhibition (DATE), 2019.

WORKING EXPERIENCES

Graduate Research Assistant

July. 2020 – present

Advisor: Dr. Tsung-Yi Ho

THETA Lab, NTHU, Hsinchu

Focus on the research about federated learning system and sophisticated adversarial attack. Jointly work with Prof.
Yiran Chen in Duke University

R&D Intern in Microsoft Taiwan Azure IoT team

Jul. 2017 - Jun. 2018

Mentor: Cheryl Hsu, Cloud Solution Architect

Taipei, Taiwan

 Built POC (covers Smart City/Retail/Home/Manufacturing) leveraging Azure IoT Cloud services todemonstrate IoT solutions to 10+ technical business partners.

Microsoft 2017 Coding Angel, R&D Leader

 Designed/Created Azure Machine Learning hands-on materials with Microsoft MVPs and delivered the workshop in coding angel event to 100+ college STEM female students.

PROFESSTIONAL Skills AND ACTIVITIES

Invited talk at CYBERSEC - Aug. 20. 2020

 Giving a keynote about "CloudLeak: DNN Model Extractions from Commercial MLaaS Platforms" at CYBERSEC Taiwan 2020, one of the largest cybersecurity conference and exhibition in the Asia Pacific Region.

Programming Languages

- C/C++, Python, Verilog, etc.
- Package: Deep Learning Framework (ex: Tensorflow, Pytorch), Scikit-Learn, Keras, etc.

Certification

Microsoft Professional Program Certificate in Data Science

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

First stand of Viola in National Tsing Hua University Orchestra

Have 10+ years performance experiences

Student Association of Computer Science Department in NTHU

Student Association Leaders Section

Computer Science Camp Leaders Section

Sep.2014 – June. 2018

Sep. 2016 – Jul. 2017

Jul. 2016 / Jul. 2017